I said I'd go out like I think we made thank you ghost here I go
You walking down to the pier
I'll go up here first, and then I'll go up and I'll get
Early and then I um
Then we're there. Hey, this is a vertical stream. Yeah
So let's go it's a beautiful day. It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood
So let's see when people start coming on in
Okay, we're doing some IRL today guys. I don't see anybody here yet
Hi, go ahead and comment in the chat. Hey, we're doing an IRL
And maybe I'll even eat the
Because I'm going it's not happy hour. I don't know if they have even half happy hour on Saturday, but
This time really good, I haven't had a nice face of chocolate going a while from the pier
That's like five or six bucks
I'm hungry now. Maybe I'll pick up a couple of twisted cheese
Yeah
Okay
how are we doing guys am i doing it right like the vertical streaming
i'm holding my phone horizontally
i almost got hit by a car whoa that way yep
Okay. Here, look at my new pants.
Okay, so...
See, I'm already at the beach.
I live in a nice little area.
we're gonna go to the famous fish market here this fish market is really really
good it's probably one of the biggest fish markets in California it's been
here probably since like the 40s or 50s it's called quality seafood and just
power plant with all these whales painted on it.
Kind of see it.
Crossing, crossing.
It's a little bit of a walk.
Oh, there's some live music out here.
Let's see what's going on over here.
I hear live music coming from some place.
See, look at all this.
This is all the boats.
People like to live on a boat. I think the high must live here someplace, huh?
See a fire truck
Hey, look there's a whole party over here. Oh
Here she comes
okay guys you did it got me off my butt look at it's a whole big event here this is called the
seaside lagoon it's the only one as a kid it's like kind of like a little playground it's like
kind of like a park but it's like on the beach all right
Okay, here we go.
What an appropriate song after that sucky mystery. Hey, look at the whole, there's a whole thing.
Whoa, here she comes.
Hi guys.
I'm not wearing any pants. I am so
I'm wearing my my cheap sandals though
Hell again
You see the pity you dog, okay
Tell me where you got club
Okay, how are we doing guys? Oh
Alexander it could have cost me more it could have cost me a lot more than that
This is I just say this you Larry are careful. Why do you have porno?
Ready to go on on your stream yard. I know it on stream yard. Yeah, or I don't know
Or else, or yeah, I was 25 spankings.
Okay, that's a little bit gay. I'm sorry. Okay.
I just paid the $25, so you don't get any more gay jokes, but that'd just be me. Okay, um,
uh, I'm kidding. Oh, oh, shit. 10% battery? Oh, fuck, I should have, like, thought harder. Okay,
well, I guess I'll, my phone might die, but it gets to 1%, I should have charged it more.
but i think i'll be able to get to the fish taco place i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
hoof it over there oh my gosh there's one bend to go over um i'm gonna hoof it
okay
i got these pants on team up for like eight dollars a great deal
it's better than an ai song okay whoa here she comes
It's like a real exciting kind of area. It's like it's bustling over here. Yeah, I haven't been out here for a while.
I can devour a fish taco on camera.
Your minutes. I am sorry that I didn't bring more battery power.
That's something I need to work out, but I'll be able to get to the pier and hopefully order some food and
Hopefully eat it on camera and I'll be able to pick up a couple
Twisted teas and a couple cigars
But Alexander that really would help me right now because any money on YouTube that I make I
Will not get for at least until I mean, but I've already get past month
Past like let's see 20 days won't come till next month because they cut it off like everything. I don't know
Don't know how they do it. It's just a little tight right now. Okay, here we go
Here. Oh there it is
Think I'm about to pass. Yeah
Here we go
There's your men around here
Whoo sweaty already
It's hot today, it's hot, oof.
Trying to go as fast as I can so my battery doesn't die.
The world's best homemade churros.
I had a pretty good churro the other day.
It was from Jack in the Bus.
It's really hot.
Oh, there's a big line out there.
Well, I'll have to handle it.
There's a skate park over there.
Oh, it smells fishy.
This is a white board.
Yeah, it's been worked out.
Yeah.
You're gonna have to do it if you didn't do it.
You can do it if you didn't do it.
I can't do materials.
I'm not a caretaker.
I'm not about to let you down.
I'm not gonna let you off.
You know?
I'm not busy this.
Sure.
Well, Alexander, no more hot dogs.
It's not a hot dog eating contest, okay?
It's on its boat.
I don't know if it's a male lion or not.
You guys are you guys are in line, okay, yeah, yes
Now it says the orientation is locked, so I have to
I am flying suit I'm tired
I'm so tired. I really am tired.
They're like five years younger, huh?
Okay, I do apologize if my
camera goes out because
I do have like
10% they're calling for the guy to like put more people through
Like people are people are just cutting in front of the line
Okay, it's like a long line
People get these big trays of food. I got big that's right. It's all full of seafood
Okay, I'll be next
Oh, there's another line developing behind me.
So, I'm going to get some fish chocolate.
Okay, thank you.
They have a $100 Lobster Lovers bucket.
Now some day, you want to support me for that.
Are there any cute guys around here?
Could this be love?
Nick, did you start?
You said Queer at the Pier. That was Nick's idea. Queer at the Pier, Carol.
I haven't done that yet.
I don't have my I don't have my cards with me. I forgot my card guys. I just say this is a very spontaneous
Okay
I'm the last person in the line
Okay, well taking a little bit long
All right, what are you guys doing?
Hopefully, how much battery power do I have?
6%
Hopefully it's not too long. It's crowded today. I think we're getting in the front of the line
It's pretty good, huh?
Yeah, we're getting up there.
Smells so good.
Firefighter? Yeah, we got a reading about...
That was a reading I got.
Yeah, they're corn, it's really good.
I think I put the city on the map though for the for the IRL and the most
famous IRLer in Rigaundo it smells so good
taking forever
All right, fish taco.
Yeah.
I thought I'd burn my wallet for a second, but I haven't.
Hungry.
I know.
That one man was Shannon was making fun of me. She's like, oh, he's hitting on the
I'm a guy at the fish the butcher and so I don't even remember hitting on the foot
Okay, I do apologize if my camera goes out three twenty minutes
Hi, can you do my order, sir?
Okay, we're almost there.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, they should be ready soon, but I'm just gonna go over Gabe Park's thing.
He was going on over there.
Let's walk over in their photo.
Okay, here we go. Let's do that mural
Skaters
Do the guys have any tricks
Like I've got a mask
Kind of hot
a firefighter do you think anyway it's not like really that busy over there okay I
think my talk good just have one talk going to be ready I'm gonna eat it on
like a five-second free this would be really cool place
I know and there's no way I hear really if I lose you guys
I'll be back.
Yum!
Den hat sie gehabt.
I stuffed that taco. There's bomb. Okay guys, that was a success.
You got some nutrition? Who is that guy without a shirt?
But that's it
My phone's probably gonna die in a minute, but I'm walking up
Take a couple drinks and some stokies
I'm gonna go home
Okay, I hope you guys enjoyed
Bish taco at the pier day. Thank you so much for ghosts for sponsoring our little
excursion
Not a breath I'm gonna go until the the wheels fall off with a aka the batteries of the phone die
That's cool, huh the nice little
Excursion might be of old times
You know a couple months ago
Going to the pier
You can have a taco
Whoa